wirelessgalaxy.com 2001-04-05

# Security and privacy Statement of Wirelessgalaxy.com

> > Our Commitment to Your Privacy:

> > > Wirelessgalaxy.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of all of our users. The following discloses our information-gathering and dissemination practices for all Wirelessgalaxy.com's sites:
>> 
>> Security:
>>
>>> Your online transactions are safely encrypted and sent over Secure Socket layers(SSL) and processed in on Secure Servers. We also email you an invoice so you can keep a record of your order. We also mail a hard copy of your order to your permanent address, in case if your order was a gift shipment. If you have further questions concerning security, please feel free to email us at [customerservice@wirelessgalaxy.com](mailto:customerservice@wirelessgalaxy.com). We will be happy to assist you.

> > Your Personal Information:
>>
>>> Please be assured that None of the personal information you provide us, including your e-mail address, will be shared with anyone unless we have your prior knowledge and consent. Your personal information will be used only to make you aware of special offers available through Wirelessgalaxy.com.
>> 
>> Emails:
>>
>>> Your email box will not be filled with Junk or Spam Emails from our Customer Service Department. Your Email address will Not be sold or contributed to Anyone else.    
> In Case you have joined WirelessGalaxy.com's Mailing list to Inform you of the latest Sales and Rebates, you will only recieve not more than 2 emails per month. Thats Our Promise.

Copyright © 1999-2000 WirelessGalaxy.com
